# **Darren Williams**

Web Developer / Graphic Designer

Address: 7 Jillian Street, Mooroolbark, VIC, 3138 - Mobile: 0417 204 809 - D.O.B: 20/04/1988 - Email: Darren@studio17designs.com.au

### **ABOUT ME**

A highly motivated and results driven professional, with 10 years' experience with in competitive and changing environments. Demonstrated competence to deliver operational and financial results, identify opportunities, resolve issues and achieve success.

Strong interpersonal skills, written and verbal communication skills, demonstrated negotiation skills along with analytical and relationship development abilities. An inherent knowledge of the graphic design and web development, a always increasing knowledge of software development with strong networks within the industries.

### **EXPERIENCE**

# WEB DEVELOPER AND PROJECT MANAGER - July 2021 - Current Walking Track Media (WFH)

- Consulted with clients to identify key requirements, define project scope, developed project plan and schedule.
- Provided leadership to internal teams on projects and daily issue resolution.
- Collaborated with clients, third party software partners and internal teams on projects.
- Publish multiple site from development to production
- Produce clean and effective code for Magento 2 sites.
- · Build single page sites using HTML, CSS and Javascript.

# WEB DEVELOPER AND GRAPHIC DESIGNER - 2019 - 2021 OPS Gateway / The Public Brewery Group (TPBG)

- Assist in development of repair management software using HTML, CSS, MongoDB and ReactJS.
- Build websites for TPBG companies, using wordpress and elementor.
- Develop online contract software using PHP and MYSQL.
- Design complete brand for Public Brewing Co, this includes logo, colours, website, product design and advertising.

## WEB DEVELOPER / GRAPHIC DESIGNER / OWNER - 2012 - CURRENT

### Studio17 Designs

- Create Logo's for established companies
- Design apparel
- Design event posters
- Design vehicle wraps
- Create Wordpress Ecommerce website using variety of page builders (elementor, Oxygen).

#### WEB DEVELOPER - 2018 - CURRENT

#### **Personal Projects**

- Built a prediction model for horse racing using python, machine learning, numpy, pandas, mysql, BeautifulSoup and Scrapy.
- Currently building project management application using react js, node, mysql, html, bootstrap and css.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### 2018 - 2019

Diploma Web Development - UpSkilled

KEY SKILLS HTML CSS Javascript React JS MySql Python PHP Magento